Yes, it's finally here!
The second Olavart YouTube project!
Yay!
In the open like this.
Where am I? That's what I'm talking about.
Where is everybody?
Seino!
Ramune!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Oi! Oi! Hey!
Whoa!
Ooh! Over there!
Whoo-hoo!
Come on!
Where are you going?
Oh, man!
Brother, it's the first night market of my life.
Let's do it! Just in time!
Whoo!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Yeah!
Yeah!Yay!
Not yet!
After the 100 km station, we came to the campsite, so we went to Laban's playground.
There was also a river!
Well, everyone be careful not to jump into the river by mistake!
Next scene, we're flopping in the river.
50 meters, I think.
I'll bring it to you at the river 100 km station.
Absolutely impossible, absolutely impossible.
I don't remember anyone who has ever been camping.
People from the country do it.
People from the countryside do it.
They do it.
Like Haruma. He's the type to go to a deserted island by himself.
If there's a bear or something... you can count on Haruma.
February Clove.
Take this.
We should split it up.
I'll tell him this too.
Sure thing.
Okay, 333.
I've got a lot of money, so let's go with 333.
Rangana.
I'm a man. I'm sorry it's such a simple task.
Open it.Yes open
2 months clove
Right.
We have to do it together.
I'm doing the heavy lifting on my own.
Ooh.
Mm-hmm.
Good luck.
Is this one supposed to go with this?
I don't know.
Is this one right? Haruma.
I'm sweating.
Is this right? This...
It goes up here.
It stopped.
There's a click.
Oh, there it is.
It's got it. It's got it.
Okay, okay.
Okay, it just clicked.
That's it.
Wow, it worked!
It's good!
It looks good, doesn't it? This view.It's nice, isn't it? I mean, this view.
It's great!
The view is great!
It's great.
It's great!
So, that's our base camp.
Our base camp
Cool hunting is complete!
I was sweating a lot even after just a little bit of light activity.
I was sweating like crazy!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to sweat a lot more!
Oh no!
I'd like to do a lot of activities.
But it's no fun to just do them, right?
Yes, it is!
Camping is about food!
Camping food
This is very important, isn't it?
Everyone wants to eat good food, right?
Let's put the ingredients for that camp food on the table.
Now...
We will be divided into 3 teams
We're going to have a showdown!I would like to confront him!
pastel
Ukisho: No, first place goes to the luxury food!
Second place goes to the standard camping course
Shichi-Go-San-Kake, pretty good
Third place goes to the original camp food course!
This is great!
It's good.
First of all, that's bad...
The green color of this chef's tape is pretty bad.
The green color is bad!
It's like a normal buster.
Insects...
Around there...
There you go.
The team with the most girls wins.
Open?
Okay.
Wait, what?
Okay!
One, two, three, okay?
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!Whoa!
Whoa!
Yes, we're all on Team Eye!
We're all on Team Eye!
Should we name the team something?
Well, let's just call it something masculine.
We'll just call ourselves Team Eye.
We're a team of men!
Thank you for watching!
We're number two.
Team, let's see...
We're the JKs who remember the hearts of pretty maidens.
Wow! Great team!
Yes, we're number three.
I think I'm going to eat a bug.
I'd like to eat a bug.
I'm not afraid of anything.
You're the strongest!
So, now that the commercial has been decided.
We're going to have a lot of food and activities!
Let's move!
Yay!
We've got something we want to do, don't we?We've got something we want to try, right?
Yeah!
Let's go, guys! Ready!
Here they come!
Are we there yet?
Yes, sir.
Hey, everyone, let's get dressed now.
This is Mino-chan, our installer!
Yay!
Nice to meet you!
I'll also ask what I'm going to be taking care of,
Here it is!
The first project!
Skyac!
иutube
Extend your right hand in front of you.
The left hand goes around the wrist to the side of the face.
Right.
Then I'll start again before I surprise you back to the left side.
And then just move your right hand forward.
Repeat like that.
Back to front.
That's right.Okay.
I'm going to ask you to extend your right hand forward.
Left hand around the side of your face so that it goes around your wrist.
Okay.
Back to front.
If you can get him to go from back to front, he can fall back or brake.
Please pedal as hard as you can using these three types.
Yes, sir.
How fast can you go?
How fast?
Yes, sir.
If you're breathing well, you'll be able to spill at the right time.
Oh, wow.
Let's see what you've been doing for the past seven years. Nine years.
Let's see your 9-year bond. I'm counting on you.
Okinawan blood makes me excited. I'll bump into it and drop it.
I'll bump and drop you so hard...
We'll go first! Power!
Team power, power, power!
Yes, sir!
Let's go!
Wow!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
I'm sorry
Oh, it's cold!Oh, it's cold.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
That's persistent.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, like this.
One, two, one, two.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four...
One, two,
Wow, that's hard!
One, two..,
One, two,
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
We're seriously on our own on that one.
This is awesome!
Oreran
Yusada seo Tsunes
It's called
dri
Good to be told or forgetYou can forget about being told.
Oh yes, we are 1 not too furry with the kettle paper like this, bad.
Th.
I thought it was quiet, but it's like they're already gone.
It sure feels like they're coming back.
I'm scared
I'll go.
Whew!
That's it.
I'm sorry.
That's too scary.
It's fine.
I'm scared.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you okay?
What's that?
Whoa.
Let's do it again from the left.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three. - Four.
Four.
Direction of rotation
WOW.Wow.
Wow.
Direction to turn
One turn
Se-ne-o
Three.
Four.
Yes! - Yes!
What do you say?
I'm a girl, so I have a girl's bond.
So, of course, I thought that Ichiki would be the best fit.
Of course.
Yes, of course.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
Ooh!
Sorry.I'm sorry.
Right? Left?
Left! Left! Left! Left!
Left! Left!
What's that? Hold on.
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
Okay, let's back up. Back up like you taught me.
Thank you for watching.
We're all here!
All right, let's go!
Left, right, left, right, left, right.
Right, left, right, left, right.
Left, right, right, left, right, left, right.
Left, right, left, right, left, right, left, right
Left Right Left Left Left Left Left Left Left Left Left Left Right
rất Reflection
Three, two, one!
Aaaaah!
Look right and left at the same time!
Straight!
Right, left, right.
Up doetdoet above
This is bad.
Does this mean it's turned?
No, it doesn't. No, it doesn't.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Watch out.
Careful. Careful.
Watch out! Watch out!
Watch your right and left.
Go, go, go, go!
Ready?
Right and left.
Shinobu Ichiro TapiShiroto
Tatsuya Shimekake
Kaito Nakamura
IBeat
The last 4!
to be continued
Hironaka Kawasaki
Nyoeru Matsui
From Tomic ره
Raba!Mule!
Mule!
Muleaaaah!!!!
A~~~~~~!!!
A~~~!!!
Woah~!!!
Yo, otoh!
Left, left, right, left, left, left, left, left.
Take your foot out. Go, go, go, go, go.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Come on, go, go, go, go, go.
Give me one more.
Yay.
Yeah!
Yay!
We're here. We're here.
I mean once it floats
I mean once it floats.Once it's up in the air.
It's over!
Congratulations.
In more ways than one.
I'm kind of done.
I'll announce the standings.
First place, Team Insect Escape.
Fantastic!
Oh, no.
I knew this was going to happen!
Cool!
Perfect for the enemy!
Second place, Team JK!
Yay!
No JK, but...
Almost first place.
Team Pose-wise.
Yay!
We came in third.
We were in last place.
Zero points!
Yes, congratulations!
You have two more. There are two more.
If we both get first place, we win.If either of them gets first place, we win.
We can win. We've only started from the beginning.
If we don't get zero points, it's going to get a little heavy.
It's true that the situation was unfolding well. We were in third place because we read the atmosphere,
We had a good combination from practice, you know.
They worked well together.
The call of "high-class lunch" was heard.
We are aiming for a high-class lunch.
We are trying to save the world of food.
If all I could think about was the food, I would always react.
I see.
Well then, I'd like to warp back to the next event location.
Here we go! Ready!
Yay!
It's so good!
Is it?
I think we have to show our true colors.
It's a show that we have to be ready for.